Davidson Ignosen, welcome to Buffalo.
The Bills select you with a 62nd overall
pick. We're so excited to have you here.
When Buffalo called your name, you were
overcome with emotion. You could tell
how much the moment meant to you. How
did that moment reflect all the hard
work that you put in? Um,
I would just say it was like
life-changing just because all the it
was a culmination of all the hard work,
all the sacrifices, the trials and the
tribulations, like the the early
mornings, the late nights. So, it just
it just validated everything that I went
through made me feel like it was worth
it.
>> The sacrifices, the trials and
tribulations to get to the NFL. Do you
point back to a moment and say that's
when I knew I was putting the work in to
really make it to the next level?
>> I mean, I put in a lot of work, but I
would say a moment that stood out to me
that I think back in my memory, I was 17
and I was packing up my stuff to leave
home, go down to Old Miss. And I mean,
the whole time I'm like, "Yeah, I'm
leaving high school early. I'm ready to
go play." But like it's not till when I
actually had to pack the car up and I
saw my brother and like I had to give
him a hug that I really broke down and
understood like I'm no longer a boy like
I'm going I'm leaving my mom's house to
go chase my dreams. I'm leaving home to
go feed home.
>> Looking back on the draft night, what's
a memory that's going to stick with you
forever?
>> Just my like I'm getting the phone call
speaking but I'm not really hearing. I'm
just feeling my mom. Like I feel like
we're attached. Like I'm feeling her
just like and she's breaking down and
I'm trying to talk on this phone but I'm
breaking down. So it just was like
breathtaking.
>> How important is your mom to you?
>> Yeah, my mom is everything. Like I said,
it's just the sacrifices that she has
she has had to just
do to just give her children
opportunity. Like my parents moved here
to America in the early '9s. So they so
they they left Nigeria just to come to
America to give their children
opportunity to be successful. when they
have to work countless number of jobs,
countless number of hours. Like growing
up, my mom never used to come into my
Pop Warner games just because she was at
work. Like if she's always working, I'm
going to I'm going to have to go if I if
I want to be successful, I'm going to
have to always be working to bust my
butt, make sure she doesn't have to work
as hard anymore.
>> Your full name means you can't argue
with God in Nigerian. How do you carry
that with you today? Yeah, I I'm I'm
Edo, born um Nigerian descent, means my
first name is I wasa means you can't
argue with God. I would say like a lot
of people have tried to write me off. A
lot of people have tried to create a
narrative for me, but you can't I'm like
I'm not fighting my own battles. The
Lord is fighting my battles for me. So
if this is what the Lord has for me,
can't argue with him.
>> The way you play the game, you invite
contact. You love the physicality
element. You called yourself a spark
plug.
>> How will your spark ignite Buffalo's
defense?
>> I'm just coming in here ready to
compete. Just being Davidson and I feel
like I don't take anything for granted.
The fact that I'm even here sitting here
talking to you is a blessing that like
don't want to take advantage
>> of any moment. So, I'm just going to
just
come in each day, ready to work, play
with passion, play with emotion, cuz I
just love football is like it's my job
now cuz I'm in the NFL. But like
football is like literally like it's
what I love to do when I'm out on the
football field. Like it's my therapy.
>> Davidson is your name. You say I'm
Davidson off the field, but I turn into
IGB on the field. Your chain says IGB.
Who is IGB on the football field?
>> IGB is a bad man on the football field.
IGB. IGB wants smoke with whoever
wherever. Like he he he is a a ultra
competitor. He's a dog. So like when I'm
off the football field, I'm Davis again.
I'm relaxed, calm. When I'm on that
field, I'm ready to go.
>> You invite the smoke. You want to
inflict the pain. You call yourself a
tone setter. How do you flip that
switch?
>> It's pretty easy. I would just say like
um
IGB if he was in the normal world it
would probably wouldn't work out
probably wouldn't be successful.
Probably would run into probably some
issues. So I feel like I'm just like on
the field I can I can exert my power. I
can I can establish my dominance over
someone. But on the football off the
football field I try to spread love off
the field.
>> You have a tall frame, long arms, 6'2,
190 lbs. You're known for your press man
ability. How have your long arms become
such a weapon?
>> I would say at the line of scrimmage
>> cuz you know a lot of receivers don't
want to get touched. They like to be
pretty. They like to do their dance
moves. Feel like if I put these hands on
you, you can't dance no more. You got to
get right into it.
>> You link back up with former college
teammate, current Bills defensive back
Jordan Hancock. What's the best thing he
told you about Buffalo?
>> Mr. Hancock, that's my boy. Yeah. Um, he
just says the best thing is the people
in the building. Like he says that this
is a special it's a special group of
people in this building that they're
they're going to help me get to where I
want to go.
>> What are three words that best represent
Davidson's personality?
>> Davidson is intelligent.
Davidson is curious.
And Davidson is ambitious. Davidson
wants just he wants more for himself. He
wants more for the people around him.
>> What's one thing that most people don't
know about you?
>> There's a lot of things that people
don't know about me. Like people people
like they see me on social media. Like
I'm really like people who know me
really know like I'm really a nerd. Like
deep down like I love books. I love
historical documentaries. I just learn I
just I I love to learn. I learn to love
to learn new things.
>> Loving history. What part of history do
you find yourself nerding out over? I
love all history. But right now, I'm
focused on African history because I
feel like in in schools, we didn't learn
a lot about I mean, I'm African, so I
didn't learn a lot about my history. We
learned a lot learn about European
history, American history. So, I I I
just try to learn about the areas that I
wasn't talking about enough.
>> Let's do some rapid fire questions. You
have a great sense of fashion. What's
your style?
>> My style is just who Davidson is. That's
how I express myself. Sometimes I'm
talking right now. Now, I'm in a talking
mood right now, but might you might
catch me where I don't want to talk
sometimes. So, I feel like I let my I
let my outfits do the talking and just
like just being true to myself cuz I got
a lot of friends and I got brothers. So,
like I I put on a fit, they tell me,
"Nah, this is it's not good. Take it
off." I'm like, "Bro, this is me. Just
let me be me."
>> We're excited to see those fits on game
day. They're going to be amazing
>> for sure.
>> What are some crazy pregame rituals that
you have?
>> I don't have crazy pregame rituals. Like
pregame I'm listening to gospel music.
Okay. Because like IGB is already on go.
IGB is trained to go. Like I need
something to calm me down, relax. Like I
don't need do nothing crazy.
>> What's one thing you can't live without?
>> The Lord.
>> Can't live Can't live without them.
>> What's your favorite food?
>> A pounded GM and a goosey. It's um a
Nigerian dish that my mom be making.
>> Okay. Yum. We might all have to try some
here in Buffalo.
>> You love the Sopranos. Yes. Who's your
favorite character?
>> Tony.
>> Tony's a bad Tony. Tony's a bad man. Uh,
yeah. I like Tony. He's He's very
He has a his his personality. He has a
very full personality. Like he's a he's
he's different.
>> Finally, what is one thing you want to
tell your new fan base? Bill's Mafia.
You can look right there.
>> Y getting a dog. If you if just ask
around, do y'all research about me
everywhere I go, bring success and I'm
here to win. So, just appreciate y'all
for having me and I'm not going to take
anything for granted. I'm maximize every
opportunity that I get. I'm grateful to
be here.
>> IGB, we're happy to have you here. We
can't wait to see you on the field.
>> Thank you.